Bulletin of Tufts Graduate School of Biomedical Sciences UP210
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Bulletin of Tufts Graduate School of Biomedical Sciences
1983 -- 2020
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences
Tufts Graduate School of Biomedical Sciences
UP210
0.5 Linear Feet
13 Digital Object(s)
9.9 Megabytes
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Biographical / Historical
The Tufts Graduate School of Biomedical Sciences was first established as the Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences by the trustees of Tufts University on July 1, 1980 through the gifts of the late Dr. Arthur M. Sackler, Dr. Mortimer D. Sackler and Dr. Raymond R. Sackler. Their vision was matched by that of current president of Tufts University, Jean Mayer, who saw integration across all medical fields as crucial for advancement of health. As a result of the generosity of the Sackler brothers, six fledging graduate programs at Tufts University School of Medicine were given a home. These programs: Biochemistry, Immunology, Molecular Biology and Microbiology, Anatomy, Pharmacology and Experimental Therapeutics, and Physiology; and their faculty of 70 provided the foundation on which our school is built. These faculty and their students were a part of the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences prior to the founding of the Sackler School. In December 2019, the name of the School was changed from the Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences to the Tufts Graduate of Biomedical Sciences due to role of the Sackler family and their company, Purdue Pharma, in the opioid epidemic.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the bulletin for the Tufts Graduate School of the Biomedical Sciences (formerly the Sackler School). It provides information for prospective students, including faculty listing, programs offered, financial aid information, and history of the school.
- Bulletin of Tufts Graduate School of Biomedical Sciences, 1983 -- 2020; 1983 -- 1998; UP210.001; 0.5 Linear Feet; 13 Digital Object(s); 9.9 Megabytes
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains the bulletin for the Tufts Graduate School of the Biomedical Sciences (formerly the Sackler School). It provides information for prospective students, including faculty listing, programs offered, financial aid information, and history of the school.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Bulletin of Tufts Universtiy Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, 1983 -- 1984; UP210.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts Universtiy Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, 1984 -- 1985; UP210.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts Universtiy Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, 1985 -- 1986; UP210.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts Universtiy Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, 1986 -- 1987; UP210.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts Universtiy Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, 1987 -- 1988; UP210.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts Universtiy Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, 1988 -- 1989; UP210.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts Universtiy Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, 1989 -- 1990; UP210.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts Universtiy Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, 1990 -- 1991; UP210.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts Universtiy Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, 1991 -- 1992; UP210.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts Universtiy Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, 1992 -- 1993; UP210.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts Universtiy Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, 1993 -- 1994; UP210.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts Universtiy Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, 1994 -- 1995; UP210.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts Universtiy Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, 1996 -- 1997; UP210.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Bulletin of Tufts Universtiy Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences, 1997 -- 1998; UP210.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Sackler Bulletin, Fall 2014; UP210.000027; 1 Digital Object(s); 670.35 Kilobytes
    Sackler Bulletin for the Fall 2014 semester.
  - Sackler Bulletin, Spring 2015; UP210.000028; 1 Digital Object(s); 675.14 Kilobytes
    Sackler Bulletin for the Spring 2015 semester.
  - Sackler Bulletin, Fall 2015; UP210.000029; 1 Digital Object(s); 636.67 Kilobytes
    Sackler Bulletin for the Fall 2015 semester.
  - Sackler Bulletin, Spring 2016; UP210.000030; 1 Digital Object(s); 659.18 Kilobytes
    Sackler Bulletin for the Spring 2016 semester.
  - Sackler Bulletin, Fall 2016; UP210.001.00003; Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences; 1 Digital Object(s); 0.67 Megabytes
    Sackler Bulletin, Fall 2016
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Transferred by Tufts Technology Services, 2016, accession 2017.022.
  - Sackler Bulletin, Spring 2017; UP210.001.00004; 1 Digital Object(s); 0.69 Megabytes
    Sackler Bulletin, Spring 2017
    Transferred by Tufts Technology Services, 2017, accession UP-2018-012.
  - Sackler Bulletin, Fall 2017; UP210.001.00005; 1 Digital Object(s); 0.71 Megabytes
    Sackler Bulletin, Fall 2017
  - Sackler Bulletin, Spring 2018; UP210.001.00006; 1 Digital Object(s); 0.7 Megabytes
    Sackler Bulletin, Spring 2018
    Transferred by Tufts Technology Services, 2018, accession UP-2018-033.
  - Sackler Bulletin, Fall 2018; UP210.001.00007; 1 Digital Object(s); 0.48 Megabytes
    Sackler Bulletin, Fall 2018
  - Sackler Bulletin, Spring 2019; UP210.001.00008; 1 Digital Object(s); .72 Megabytes
    Sackler Bulletin, Spring 2019
  - Sackler Bulletin, Fall 2019; UP210.000025; 491 Kilobytes
    Sackler Bulletin, Fall 2019
  - Graduate School of Biomedical Sciences Bulletin, Spring 2020; UP210.000026; 1.47 Megabytes
    Graduate School of Biomedical Sciences Bulletin, Spring 2020
  - Graduate School of Biomedical Sciences Bulletin, Fall 2020; UP210.000031; 1.3 Megabytes
    Graduate School of Biomedical Sciences Bulletin, Fall 2020